<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on PaperFoo</title>
    <link>https://paperfoo.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on PaperFoo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 15:41:45 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paperfoo.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Design Philosophy of the DARPA Internet Protocols</title>
      <link>https://paperfoo.com/posts/internet-protocols-design-philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 15:41:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperfoo.com/posts/internet-protocols-design-philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Summary of David D. Clark&amp;rsquo;s 1988 paper titled &amp;ldquo;The Design Philoshophy of the DARPA Internet Protocols&amp;rdquo;.
Main idea: 
Why is the TCP/IP Internet protocol suite designed the way it is? 
This paper is an attempt to highlight some of the early reasoning behind the architectural decisions taken while designing the Internet protocols.
Two key ideas:
 the datagram (or connectionless service) layering of separate IP and TCP layers  These ideas were not part of the original proposal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of Papers</title>
      <link>https://paperfoo.com/posts/list-of-papers-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 20:30:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paperfoo.com/posts/list-of-papers-draft/</guid>
      <description> A brief history of the internet A Unified Theory of Garbage Collection The Dangers of Replication and a Solution Dynamic Adaptive Streaming over http Sun NFS file system Randomized Search Trees Development of the Domain Name System FlexSC (also check the nice summary from lobsters) Bitcoin Time, Clocks and the Ordering of Events in a Distributed System Skiplist Heap Architectures for Concurrent Languages using Message Passing The UNIX Time sharing System Ethereum: A secure decentralized generalised transaction ledger An Incremental Approach to Compiler Construction A Relational Model of Data for Large Shared Data Banks The case for the reduced instruction set computer New Directions in Cryptography (Diffie-Hellmann) A Rational Design Process&amp;ndash;How and Why to Fake It Read a paper: Unikernels and Linux Python 3 Types in the Wild Evolution of the Unix System Architecture: An Exploratory Case Study Purely functional Red-Black trees LLVM: A Compilation framework for lifelong analysis and transformation A Comprehensive Study of Autonomous Vehicle Bugs The Tail at Scale Performance evolution of Linux’s core operations Fast, Interactive Origami Simulation using GPU Computation Quicksort A Method for the Construction of Minimum-redundancy codes - Huffman RAFT: Recurrent All-Pairs Field Transforms for Optical Flow    Curvature and Creases: A primer on Paper (David Huffman)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
